Academic Departments - Record Group 9 WLU.RG.0009
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
- Music Department
  - Programs, 2016-09-18-2017-05-23; 30 Item
    - The Senior Composition Recital, Bennett F. O. Lewis, 2017-03-18; 1 Item
      Lewis, Bennett F. O.
    - Senior Voice Recital, Jake Burnett '17, baritone, 2017-03-19; 1 Item
      Burnett, Jake; Yen, Ting-Ting
    - Southeastern Composers League 2017 Forum, 2017-03-24-2017-03-25; 1 Item
      Southeastern Composers' League
    - Oratorio and Concerto Concert, 2017-03-28; 1 Item
      Washington and Lee University. University Orchestra; Washington and Lee University. Choir; Dobbins, Christopher; Lynch, Shane; Hurst, Conley
    - University Wind Ensemble and Chamber Winds NEW HORIZONS, 2017-04-04; 1 Item
      Washington and Lee University. University Wind Ensemble; Eckhardt, Louie; Thomas, Omar; Washington and Lee University. Chamber Winds
    - Celebrating Student Soloists, University Jazz Ensemble, 2017-04-06; 1 Item
      Washington and Lee University. University Jazz Ensemble; Vosbein, Terry
    - Guest Piano Recital, 2017-04-28; 1 Item
    - The Schumann-Brahams Connection, Marlbrook Chamber Players, 2017-05-07; 1 Item
      Washington and Lee University. Marlbrook Chamber Players; McArdle, Jaime; Yen, Ting-Ting; Gaylard, Timothy
    - Senior Piano Recital, 2017-05-14; 1 Item
      Gorman, Eliie; McDonnell, Ryan
    - Senior Piano Recital, 2017-05-23; 1 Item
      Hurst, Conley
  - Programs, 2017-2018
    Washington and Lee University. Lenfest Center for the Arts; Washington and Lee University. Department of Music
  - Programs, 2018-09-08-2019-05-21; Washington and Lee University. Department of Music; Washington and Lee University. Lenfest Center for the Arts; 43 Item
  - Programs, 2019-09-21-2019-12-05; 14 Item
  - Programs, 2020-01-31-2020-11-07; 10 Item
  - Programs, 2021-01-29-2021-05-01; Washington and Lee University. Department of Music; 9 Item
  - Programs, 2021-09-12-2022-05-25; Washington and Lee University. Department of Music; 36 Item
  - Programs, 1993-4-28-2014-03-30
  - The Sonoklect Letter, 1996-09-2017-03
- Philosophy Department
  - 18th Century Natural Philosophy and 20th Century America, Presented by Prof. Taylor Sanders, History and Prof. Tom Williams, Physics, Washington and Lee University, Sanders, Irwin T. (Irwin Taylor); Williams, Tom
- Physics and Engineering Department
- Politics Department
- Psychology Department
- Religion Department
- Romance Languages Department
  - Summer Language Institute for Secondary Teachers of French and Spanish, 1965; 2 Item
- Sociology and Anthropology
  - Liberty Hall Archaeology Program brochures, 1973-1977; 6 Item
- Theater, Dance, and Film Studies Department
  - Theatre Production Programs, Undated
  - Programs of the Troubadour Theatre, 1933-1964
  - Theatre Programs, 2016-2022; Washington and Lee University. Department of Theater, Dance, and Film Studies; 14 Item
    See Also RG 48 Lenfest
    - The Theory of Relativity. Music and Lyrics by Neil Bartram. Book by Brian Hill. Directed by Rob Mish '76. Music direction by Steven Gross., 2016-10-20-2016-10-23; Washington and Lee University. Department of Theater, Dance, and Film Studies; 1 Item
    - W&L Dancers Create...., 2016-11-10,11,12-2019-12-4,5,6; Washington and Lee University. Department of Theater, Dance, and Film Studies; 2 Item
    - Dracula by Steven Dietz, based on the novel by Bram Stoker. Directed by Jemma Alix Levy., 2017-02-09-2017-02-12; Washington and Lee University. Department of Theater, Dance, and Film Studies; 1 Item
    - W&L Repertory Dance Company, 2017-03-17, 18, 19-2019-03-29, 30, 31; Washington and Lee University. Department of Theater, Dance, and Film Studies; 2 Item
    - Priscilla Queen of the Desert, 2018-10-25-2018-10-28; Washington and Lee University. Department of Theater, Dance, and Film Studies; 1 Item
    - Vanya and Sonia and Masha and Spike, 2018-11-11-2018-11-14; Washington and Lee University. Department of Theater, Dance, and Film Studies; Washington and Lee University. Lenfest Center for the Arts; 1 Item
    - The Cherry Orchard, 2019-03-12-2019-03-17; Washington and Lee University. Department of Theater, Dance, and Film Studies; Washington and Lee University. Lenfest Center for the Arts; 1 Item
    - Legally Blonde, 2016-03-10-2016-03-14
      Washington and Lee University. Department of Theater, Dance, and Film Studies
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 2019-10-31-2019-11-03; Shakespeare, William; Gary, Dana; 1 Item
      Directed by Jemma Alix Levy and music composed by Dana Gary WLU 2018.
      Levy, Jemma Alix
    - W&L Dancers Create..., 2019-11-14-2019-11-16; 1 Item
    - Everybody, 2020-03-12-2020-03-15; 1 Item
      Directed by Stephanie Sandberg and written by Branden Jacobs-Jenkins.
      Sandberg, Stephanie
    - Tartuffe, 2020-10-15-2020-10-18; 1 Item
      Directed by Stephanie Sandberg, written by Moliere, and adapted by Ranjit Bolt.
    - W&L Dancers Create..., 2020-11-05-2020-11-07; 1 Item
      Celester Lanuza, Artistic Director.
      Lanuza, Celeste
    - W&L Repertory Dance Concert., 2021-03-25-2021-03-28; 1 Item
      Shaleigh Comerford, Artistic Director.
      Comerford, Shaleigh
    - Burn, 2021-04-09-2021-04-10; 1 Item
      Written by Devorah Gearing and directed by Jemma Alix Levy.
    - Thumbelina, 2022-02-12; 1 Item
    - The Dramatic Circle., 2021-12-02-2021-12-05; 1 Item
    - W&L Dance Create..., 2021-11-11-2021-11-13; 1 Item
    - Heroes of the Fourth Turning, 2021-10-21-2021-10-23; 1 Item
    - W&L Repertory Dance Company & University Jazz Ensemble., 1 Item
    - tick, tick ... BOOM!, 2022-03-31-2022-04-03; 1 Item
- General
  - Curriculum Survey Results, 1975
    A bound computer printout showing course results from the Fall 1975 term.